<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>JD DE MONTEVERDE</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content on JD DE MONTEVERDE</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Homelab</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/projects/my-first-project/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/projects/my-first-project/</guid>
      <description>This is my self hosted homelab using my old laptop</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My First Static Website</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/projects/my-second-project/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/projects/my-second-project/</guid>
      <description>My first website that I created from scratch</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Self Hosting Container Registry</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blogs/self-hosting-container-registry/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blogs/self-hosting-container-registry/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This blog is to just share what is my thought process on why I wanted to build Harbor my self hosted container registry.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;My portfolio website is deployed using an image pushed to my account in docker hub. For it to be pulled by my GitOps system I had to make the image publicly accessible. This is obviously insecure and someone can just use that image. So, I decided to self host a container registry.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hosting My First Portfolio Website in My Homelab</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blogs/hosting-my-first-portfolio-website-in-my-homelab/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blogs/hosting-my-first-portfolio-website-in-my-homelab/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Today is the day I successfully hosted my own portfolio website in my homelab. I started coding my portfolio around three months ago, and it was very difficult for me since I do not have a background in coding HTML, CSS, and JavaScript.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The first design of this webpage came from a YouTube channel called &lt;em&gt;How to Web Dev&lt;/em&gt;. The creator coded it live, and I manually copied the code from his video. A lot of work, right? 😄&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Started my Homelab</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blogs/started-my-homelab/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blogs/started-my-homelab/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Today is March 10, 2025, and I am writing this at 4:30 in the morning. I cannot sleep, so I just wanted to write down my thoughts about the difficulties I have faced or am currently facing while setting up my homelab.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I started “homelabing” on February 26, beginning with a simple Ubuntu Server installation on my old laptop which is a Dell Latitude 7290. I set up SSH and then successfully assigned it a static IP. That alone was a challenge for me. It took me about 10 hours just to get the static IP working, which pretty much confirms that networking is not my strong suit but that is the whole point why I started homelab. That is to have an environment where I can play and learn about the things I am not experienced at.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About Me</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/about/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Mar 2023 10:30:00 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/about/about/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Hello World! I&amp;rsquo;m passionate about technology and software development. This space is where I share my projects, experiences, and thoughts.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Feel free to explore my work and reach out if you&amp;rsquo;d like to connect!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
